

Skills

- Ambitious and Self Sufficient
- High Level of Interpersonal savvy
- Skilled Team Collaborator
- Managing Conflicts

- · Complex Problem Solving
- Action Orientated
- Bilingual (English and German)
- Adobe Suite and Final Cut Pro X

Professional Summary

I recently got the opportunity to move to Madrid and work with the British council as a to be a part time English Language Assistant. I am a motivated individual with a history of meeting and exceeding objectives. Previously working as an Apple Specialist, with a passion to help people grow and realise their own potential. I have a huge desire to learn and create new concepts and ideas wherever possible. I am very technically minded due to my university qualifications and recent job rolls. Throughout my career I have consistently worked with a wide range of existing technologies while applying new and emerging options that can enhance organisational outcomes. Continuously challenging myself to exceed expectation and widen my knowledge and skill level.

Hobbies and Interests

I started dancing salsa two years ago and haven't looked back since. I spent a lot of my free time going to classes and events around the UK, it's a great way to meet and interact with new people which is something I really enjoy. Outside of dancing I spend time with friends and family, doing new things/ attending new events in the local area. I also like to go to the gym and staying active. I like to volunteer for local charities and have over 200 hours of volunteering behind me. As I have just moved to Madrid I have been exploring the area as well making new friends and building my community here.

Experience

English Language Assistant

October 2023 - Present

CEIPSO La Luna. Revas - Madrid

- I have collaborated with teachers to design and implement dynamic lessons focusing on vocabulary and grammar for secondary school students. And have worked closely with educators to create engaging and interactive content, fostering a positive learning environment.
- I facilitated language acquisition through the development of innovative and enjoyable educational games, designed to enhance student participation and deepen understanding. I have gained valuable skills of adaptability in tailoring lesson plans to suit the diverse learning needs of students, including students with, autism, complete loss of sight and down-syndrome.
- I proactively engaged with students, fostering a positive and inclusive atmosphere within the classroom. I supported language learning objectives by incorporating fun and interactive activities, contributing to the overall enhancement of students' language skills.
- This experience not only demonstrates my collaborative approach with teachers but also emphasises my commitment to creating an enjoyable and effective learning environment for students.

Product Specialist

August 2019 to September 2023

Apple, Cribbs Causeway - Bristol

- During my time at Apple I have delivered excellent customer experiences in many environments, using strong communication skills and creative thinking to share my knowledge with customers.
- I collaborate with my team in complex situations, finding the best, full solution for every customer and troubleshooting customer enquires to solve the issue or discover next steps.

- I have lead mentoring conversations with new and current members of staff in areas they may be struggling with and continually checking in to discover what's going well and where we can improve.
- During my secondment to the business team in 2022 I quickly adapted to the new role within the
 company, by learning new software such as Slack and CRM. Supporting the growth and development
 of the client relationships. I was able to discover my strengths and opportunities within this role and
 built my resilience to support my transition in and out of the experience.
- I am highly results driven with store and personal goals in mind. I work towards quarterly goals set by myself and management. I consider myself as somebody that likes to challenge themselves and push for higher results than expected. I hold myself accountable to reach those goals, especially when I set my mind to something. During my latest annual review (August 2023), I have a score of 92 NPS and a Team Member Score of 98 as well as exceeding expectations in all over areas we are measured on. Due to this, I was the highest performing employee in my store. My AppleCare attachment on iPhone was 41% and all other products averaged at 43%.

Front of House

January 2020 to September 2023

David Lloyd Leisure - Bristol

- I delivered exceptional, friendly and fast service to process high volume of food and drink orders at peak times.
- Warmly welcomed 400+ members day and night with a smile, ensuring they were promptly served and satisfied.
- Studied and learnt popular and custom food and drink offers in order to give quality recommendations to guests.
- I ensured a safe and efficient environment by working with the team to keep a clean workplace, and maintaining equipment and stock levels.

Employment History

Chance and Counters - Boardgames Cafe (2018 - 2019) Showcase Cinema (2017 - 2018) Odeon Cinema (2015 - 2017) Waterstones Bookshop (2014 - 2015)

Education

NVQ Level 3 : Gym Instructing and Personal Training, 2022

Premier Global

Bachelor of Arts : Film Production, 2020 **Plymouth Marjon University -** Plymouth, PLY

- First Class Honours Adapting to new work environments.
- · Learning new software quickly and effectively.
- Managing multiple projects at a time and collaborating with a team across many different socialisms.
- · Working to set deadlines with quick turn over times and revisions.

A-Levels: Creative Media, 2017

Northampton College - Northampton

- A*AA Working across many different areas of study.
- Developing knowledge of softwares specific to many media outputs such as digital print, film, sound design and photography.
 animation and graphic design.
- Self lead projects and group assignments.